wordiq.com 2004-06-24

# Dictionary & Encyclopedia - Free Online Definitions

|    

**On-line Privacy Policy of wordIQ.com**

We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of the users of our sites. This privacy policy will advise you about how we protect your personal information, and about what choices you have concerning our use of such information. Please read this policy carefully. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our sites. We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this policy regularly.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please send us an e-mail to: [**support@wordIQ.com**](mailto:support@wordIQ.com).

**Scope of Privacy Policy**

This policy applies to your use of all of the sites and services owned or operated by wordIQ, and affiliated companies (collectively "wordIQ" or "we," "us," or "our"), including wordIQ.com and any other site that we may own or operate currently or in the future (collectively, the "wordIQ Sites"). Unless we say otherwise, all references to the wordIQ Sites in this policy include all such sites. This policy does not apply to your use of unaffiliated sites to which any of the wordIQ Sites only links.

**Non-Personal Identification Information And the Use of Cookie Technology**

We collect non-personal identification information through the use of "cookie" technology and/or IP address tracking. Non-personal identification information might include the browser you use, the type of computer, the operating systems, the Internet service providers and other similar information. Our system also automatically gathers information about the areas you visit on our sites and about the links you may select from within our site to other areas of the World Wide Web or elsewhere online.

We use such information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our sites. This way we know which areas of our sites are favorites of our users, which areas need improvement, and what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our sites.

We may share this aggregate statistical information with our partners, suppliers and other third parties, but we will not share any individual names, personal navigational or other personal information. Some of our advertisers may display ads on our sites which solicit or contain technology to collect information about our users for the advertisers, but we will not permit such advertisers to collect any personal information from our users within our sites.

Most browsers are set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of the wordIQ Sites may not function properly.

**Links to Other Sites**  
Users will find advertising or other contents on our sites that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. In many cases, the links represent cooperative projects or are mutual links established with persons or entities connected with our sites. Although we initially visit the sites or services that are so linked, we do not control the contents or links that appear on these sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their contents and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, or no policy (policies) at all. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.

**Security Policy**  
Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority. We have taken careful measures to secure both your information and our physical premises. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Our secure server software encrypts information, ensuring that all Internet transactions remain private (unless sent by an unsecured means, such as e-mail).

**User Agreement**  
By using any of the wordIQ Sites, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the wordIQ Sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.

(Last modified on 1/01/2004)

* * *  
  
---  
  
Copyright 2004 wordIQ All rights reserved  Privacy Policy  **::**  Terms of Use  **::**  Contact Us  **::**  About Us
